(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Deborah did a lot of push-ups yesterday.
She usually never did any at all.
When she woke up the next day, her
arms were sore.
She was confused at first.
She did not hit herself.
She wondered why her arms felt so weak.
It hurt to move them.
It really hurt when people touched her arm.
Even a small poke would hurt her.
She asked her dad to take her to
the doctor.
Her dad asked her if she had exercised.
She told him about the push-ups.
Now I see.
After you exercise a lot, you get sore
the next day, her dad said.
What can I do in order to not
get sore?
What can I do in order not to
Deborah asked.
Stretch, her dad said.